The cabin lights were settled in.
The family fast asleep.
The fireplace was embers.
A promise I couldn't keep.
I said,
"Goodnight,
my darling" and hit the flannel sheets.
You stayed out by the fire glow.
Sipping something sweet.
A bottle full of cinnamon,
they call it Fireball.
You said it's just so easy.
Leaning on the wall.
You didn't see the danger.
The sugary disguise.
Just the dancing flames reflected in your eyes.
Oh,
but 3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then a moan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plastic throne.
And I was your humble servant in the pale moonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all my might.
It wasn't wine and roses.
It wasn't graceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamon queen.
Even watching the bourbon flow.
Ha!
That devil in a bottle.
It whispers candy lies.
A liquid Trojan horse.
A burning sweet surprise.
Shot after shot went down.
Smooth as a velvet glove.
You lost all track of reason and lost all track of love.
Or sobriety.
The silence of the forest.
Shattered by the sound.
Of all that cinnamon whiskey.
Fighting the wrong way round.
Oh,
but 3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then a moan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plastic throne.
And I was your humble servant in the pale moonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all my might.
It wasn't wine and roses.
It wasn't graceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamon queen.
Even watching the bourbon flow.
Now some guys get a siren.
A goddess on a pedestal.
Mine was kneeling over.
Looking rather dreadful.
But as I held your forehead and whispered,
"It's all right."
My love was shining clearer than the stars on that cold night.
It's not the perfect moments.
It's the ones we survive that prove you're still the only one who makes me feel alive.
Oh yeah,
3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then a moan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plastic throne.
And I was your humble servant in the pale moonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all my might.
It wasn't wine and roses.
It wasn't graceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamon queen.
Even watching the bourbon flow.
Yeah.
My cinnamon queen.
A crown of messy hair.
Worship in the trash can.
But I'll always be right there.